<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>StarWars on KC Brick Emporium</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/categories/starwars/</link>
    <description>Recent content in StarWars on KC Brick Emporium</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//localhost:1313/categories/starwars/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Star Wars - 501st Clone Troopers Battle Pack</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/starwars/75345/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/starwars/75345/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Youngsters can lead their own 501st Clone Troopers unit with this LEGO® Star Wars™ Battle Pack (75345) for ages 6 and up. It features 4 new-for-January-2023 LEGO minifigures – a 501st Officer, 501st Clone Specialist and 2 501st Heavy Troopers – each with a weapon for action play. The set also includes a buildable AV-7 anti-vehicle cannon with a spring-loaded shooter and a seat for a LEGO minifigure. This popular building toy makes a cool gift for kids, letting them recreate Star Wars: The Clone Wars action and adding extra fun play possibilities to their other LEGO Star Wars sets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Step into a new way of building
Check out the LEGO Builder app for digital instructions and zoom and rotate viewing tools to enhance children’s creative experience and their sense of achievement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Galaxy of fun
The LEGO Group has been creating brick-built versions of Star Wars starships, vehicles, locations and characters since 1999. There is a huge variety of buildable models to inspire fans of all ages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Building set for battle play – With this LEGO® Star Wars™ 501st Clone Troopers Battle Pack (75345), kids can build their own Clone squadron and recreate action-packed Star Wars: The Clone Wars scenes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4 LEGO® Star Wars™ minifigures – A 501st Officer with a blaster pistol, a 501st Clone Specialist with a blaster rifle and 2 501st Heavy Troopers, each with a blaster&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Brick-built AV-7 anti-vehicle cannon – The AV-7 has adjustable legs, an elevating cannon, a spring-loaded shooter and a seat for a LEGO® minifigure&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gift idea for Star Wars™ fans aged 6+ – Give this 119-piece building toy as a birthday or holiday gift or anytime treat to kids who are into Star Wars: The Clone Wars and Star Wars: The Bad Batch&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Portable play – The cannon turret measures over 2.5 in. (7 cm) high, 2.5 in. (6 cm) wide and 5 in. (13 cm) deep. This compact set will fit in a kid’s backpack ready for play on the go&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interactive digital building – Using the LEGO® Builder app, kids can zoom, rotate and visualize a digital version of this construction model as they build&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;LEGO® Star Wars™ building toys for all ages – LEGO Star Wars sets let kids (and adult fans) recreate iconic scenes, make up their own action-adventures or simply display the buildable models&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Premium quality – LEGO® components satisfy demanding industry standards, ensuring that they connect simply and strongly for robust builds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Safety assurance – LEGO® building bricks are tested in almost every way imaginable to make sure they comply with strict global safety standards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;part-list&#34;&gt;Part List&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1I70YyFny8NVuXmbWHTyO-uonZmRIbLCb/view?usp=sharing&#34;&gt;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1I70YyFny8NVuXmbWHTyO-uonZmRIbLCb/view?usp=sharing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;building-instructions-for-75345&#34;&gt;Building instructions for 75345&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Book Number&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Instrustions Link&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://lego.com/cdn/product-assets/product.bi.core.pdf/6493750.pdf&#34;&gt;https://lego.com/cdn/product-assets/product.bi.core.pdf/6493750.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
